Solution 2
The comment tag is used to insert comments in the source code comments are not displayed are not displayed in the browser. You can use comments to explain your code ,
Which can help you when you edit the source code at a later date.

Solution 4
Tags are the starting and ending parts of an HTML element. They begin with < symbol and end with > symbol. Whatever written inside < and > are called tags.  Eg h1 tag, img, br, hr, 
Element - it consists of a starting tag, content, and an end tag.
Eg -  <h1>Heading tag of html</h1>

Solution 5
All HTML documents must start with a <!DOCTYPE> declaration.
The declaration is not an HTML tag. It is an "information" to the browser about what document type to expect.
In HTML 5, the declaration is simple: